{
    "subject": "resource/184th_Pennsylvania_Infantry",
    "predicate": "property/battles",
    "object": "resource/Battle_of_Hatcher's_Run",
    "human_readable": "The 184th Pennsylvania Infantry was involved in the Battle of Hatcher's Run.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9806713461875916,
            "question": "What battle was the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9762342572212219,
            "question": "Name a battle that the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry fought in."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9638029336929321,
            "question": "What battle is associated with the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9263120889663696,
            "question": "Was the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry involved in any major battles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8708243370056152,
            "question": "What significant event did the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry take part in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.851024866104126,
            "question": "In what historical conflict might the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry have served?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8406621813774109,
            "question": "What was the name of the engagement where the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry was present?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8257685899734497,
            "question": "Can you identify a Civil War battle that involved the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7429189085960388,
            "question": "Which military unit participated in the Battle of Hatcher's Run?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5522406697273254,
            "question": "Which military unit was present at Hatcher's Run?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The 184th Pennsylvania Infantry was involved in the Battle of Hatcher's Run.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3043_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which military unit participated in the Battle of Hatcher's Run?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3043_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you identify a Civil War battle that involved the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3043_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of the engagement where the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry was present?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3043_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3043_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3043_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3043_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3043_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3043_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3043_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3043_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3043_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3043_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3043_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provided contain information about the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry Regiment, including its engagements and battles. The specific battle mentioned in the triple is the Battle of Hatcher's Run. In one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3043/re-ranker-msmarco/13.txt), it is stated that \"October 27-28 Boydton Plank Road, Hatcher\u2019s Run\" was an engagement in which the regiment lost 15 killed and wounded. This information supports the triple, indicating that the answer should be \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided mentions that the 184th Pennsylvania Volunteer Infantry participated in various battles, including the Battle of Hatcher\u2019s Run. Therefore, the statement that the 184th Pennsylvania Infantry was involved in the Battle of Hatcher's Run is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}